<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Unknown Entity 1806</title>
<description> My little corner of the internet. Sharing my art and thoughts. </description>
<link>https://www.unknownentity1806.page/rss.xml</link>
<atom:link href="https://www.unknownentity1806.page/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<ttl>1440</ttl>
<webMaster>webmaster@unknownentity1806.page</webMaster>
<lastBuildDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:54:00 +0100 </lastBuildDate>
<language>en-us</language>
  
<!-- 
  Place your feed items here.
   -->
<item>
<guid>https://unknownentity1806.page/index.html</guid>
<title>Launch of version 2.0</title>
<description> I launched version 2.0. I just could not wait until I had every page coded in the new style. So I just went ahead and launched it as is. This will I think motivate me more to work on the new pages. This new version was made from scratch! I used no layout generator. So I was able to fully try and make what I had envisioned for this version. I am sure that version 3.0 will be even cooler as I increase my skillset. But for now I want to focus on creating more content for the website rather than thinking about improving the design. Which is why I also launched version 2.0 without having all the pages ready. Seeing version 1.2 live kept bothering me, because I wanted to change so much stuff around and the layout was not really working for me. This version feels more authentic and less like wasted space. Wow long update. Done now! </description>
<link>https://unknownentity1806.page/index.html</link>
<pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:49:35 +0100 </pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<guid>https://unknownentity1806.page/public/Blog/w-i-p/january-01.html</guid>
<title>Works in Progress January</title>
<description> A little bit of my works in progress in January. Some might be finished this month. Others are more ideas that are for further in the future. </description>
<link>https://unknownentity1806.page/public/Blog/w-i-p/january-01.html</link>
<pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 10:49:35 +0100 </pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<guid>https://unknownentity1806.page/public/Blog/2026-01.html</guid>
<title>Hello World, Hello 2026!</title>
<description> It is 2026, and this is my first blogpost! So stoked for it. I wanted to share a video I made for my old YT channel. </description>
<link>https://unknownentity1806.page/public/Blog/2026-01.html</link>
<pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:49:35 +0100 </pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>